

nicole IMAN

www.coderfoundry.com/nicoleiman

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript

JQuery Bootstrap

.NET

C# MVC

ASP.NET

SOL

LINQ

Xamarin WebAPI

CODER

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · May 2018-August 2018

- Created a personal portfolio utilizing C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery. Additionally, enhanced the site with a blog and developed the database using Code First Migrations with LINQ and Entity Framework. Additional technologies: CK Editor, Syntax Highlighter
- Fully designed and developed a multi-functional project/issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security along with file uploading features. Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC6, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables

Harris Teeter, Store Accountant / Office Assistant / Cashier Greensboro, NC · May 2012–May 2018

- Responsible for reconciling all tills and office daily
- Kept up with all bookwork and ensured it was accurate and organized
- Worked with cashiers and customer service clerks to provide excellent customer service
- Learned basics of store-level accounting, including: reconciling tills and office as well as basic bookwork

Arcadia University, Assistant Student Secretary to Provost *Glenside, PA · September 2010–December 2011*

- Worked directly with Provost and his secretary to ensure confidential budget information was filed, copied and faxed correctly
- Organized itineraries and set up meetings

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina Greensboro, French (minor in English)

Greensboro, NC · 2014

L'Universite d'Angers, Semester Abroad

Angers, France · 2013